Guide to the Vassar College Alumnae/i Biographical Files (AAVC), circa 1865-2015
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Class of 1925
  - Barlund, Ragni (Box 67)
  - Barr, Mary-Margaret H. (Box 67)
  - Bass, Ruth E. (Box 67)
  - Beach, Margaret S. (Box 67)
  - Bedford, Emily (Box 67)
  - Beer, Phyllis M. (Box 67)
  - Bennett, Margaret B. (Box 67)
  - Berdan, Mary Anna (Box 67)
  - Bernhard, Ruth M. (Box 67)
  - Bicknell, Elizabeth (Box 67)
  - Bierning, Elza (Box 67)
  - Bigelow, Charlotte (Box 67)
  - Bill, Mary F. (Box 67)
  - Blackmon, Ruth E. (Box 67)
  - Bock, Mildred Ruth (Box 67)
  - Bookner, Nancy L. (Box 67)
  - Booth, Mary E. (Box 67)
  - Bower, M. Elizabeth (Box 67)
  - Boynton, Martha C. (Box 67)
  - Bradley, Katharine (Box 68)
  - Brock, Hannah (Box 68)
  - Brooker, Gretta (Box 68)
  - Broughton, Ruth M. (Box 68)
  - Brown, Eleanor E. (Box 68)
  - Brown, Elizabeth L. (Box 68)
  - Brown, Martha (Box 68)
  - Bryant, Susanna P. (Box 68)
  - Brydon, Anne P. (Box 68)
  - Bullock, Grace Helena (Box 68)
  - Bullwinckel, Katharine (Box 68)
  - Burchard, Susan (Box 68)
  - Burchstead, Elizabeth L. (Box 68)
  - Burman, Florence K. (Box 68)
  - Burtner, Ruth B. (Box 68)
  - Butcher, Margaret (Box 68)
  - Butterfield, Caroline H. (Box 68)
  - Campbell, Ruth G. (Box 68)
  - Carpenter, Katheryn (Box 68)
  - Carter, Martha A. (Box 68)
  - Carter, Mary (Box 68)
  - Castellini, Theolinda S. (Box 68)
  - Chapman, Helen A. (Box 68)
  - Clark, Lois E. (Box 68)
  - Clarke, Elizabeth E. (Box 68)
  - Coale, Josephine (Box 68)
  - Coggeshall, Elizabeth (Box 68)
  - Coleman, Janet (Box 68)
  - Colt, Mrs. S. Barclay (Box 68)
  - Comstock, Winifred (Box 68)
  - Cook, Lilian M. (Box 68)
  - Cooke, Antoinette A. (Box 68)
  - Cosmey, Beatrice S. (Box 68)
  - Cox, Adaline P. (Box 68)
  - Crary, Ruth (Box 68)
  - Craven, Ruthwood (Box 68)
  - Crawford, M. Helen (Box 68)
  - Crutcher, Roberta (Box 68)
  - Crutchfield, Margaret (Box 68)
  - Culver, Jean E. (Box 68)
  - Cunningham, Dorothy S. (Box 68)
  - Davidson, Margaret H. (Box 68)
  - Davies, Eleanor (Box 68)
  - Davis, Catharine (Box 68)
  - Davis, Flora (Box 68)
  - De Blois, Elizabeth (Box 68)
  - Demarest, Muriel, [EMPTY] (Box 68)
  - Denton, F. Eloise (Box 68)
  - Dillard, Ruth P. (Box 68)
  - Dobson, Harriet M. (Box 68)
  - Dodge, Eleanor C. (Box 68)
  - Dorman, Isabel W. (Box 68)
  - Dreier, Antoinette S. (Box 68)
  - Duggan, Mary A. (Box 68)
  - Dutcher, Carolene (Box 68)
  - Dykes, Helen N. (Box 68)
  - Eastburn, Sara P. (Box 68)
  - Effron, Ruth (Box 68)
  - Ellis, Jean K. (Box 68)
  - Engel, Katherine T. (Box 68)
  - Engelhard, Margaret (Box 68)
  - England, Catharine H. (Box 68)
  - Evans, Doris R. (Box 68)
  - Fairfield, Wynne (Box 68)
  - Farrand, Margaret P. (Box 68)
  - Farrington, Virginia A. (Box 68)
  - Fay, Ellen L. (Box 68)
  - Ficken, Loti M. (Box 68)
  - Finch, Madeline (Box 68)
  - Fisher, Katherine B. (Box 68)
  - Fitzhugh, Anne (Box 68)
  - Flynn, Melvina L. (Box 68)
  - Foote, Katharine W. (Box 68)
  - Foster, Alice D. (Box 68)
  - Franson, Helen M. (Box 68)
  - Franz, Elizabeth P. (Box 68)
  - French, Hope Sewell (Box 68)
  - Fuller, Alfreda P. (Box 68)
  - Furnas, Marthedith (Box 68)
  - Furse, Margaret H. (Box 68)
  - Gage, Helen C., [EMPTY] (Box 68)
  - Garrison, Claire (Box 68)
  - Gaston, Gertrude F. (Box 68)
  - Gay, Elizabeth C. (Box 68)
  - George, Julie G. (Box 68)
  - Gilbert, A. Lilian A. (Box 68)
  - Gilbert, Esther (Box 68)
  - Glauser, Kathryn D. (Box 68)
  - Glicksman, Edith C. (Box 68)
  - Goell, Ruth J. (Box 68)
  - Graham, Marjorie P. (Box 68)
  - Greeley, Laura W. (Box 68)
  - Green, Gladys M. (Box 68)
  - Greminger, Marguerite E. (Box 68)
  - Griggs, Alice C. (Box 68)
  - Hall, Alice M. (Box 68)
  - Hall, Dorothy (Box 68)
  - Hall, Ruth Austin (Box 68)
  - Hanauer, Alice C. (Box 68)
  - Harnecker, C. Alicia (Box 68)
  - Harris, Barbara B. (Box 68)
  - Harris, Katharine G. (Box 68)
  - Harris, Mildred E. (Box 68)
  - Harroun, Helen E. (Box 68)
  - Hawes, Elizabeth (Box 68)
  - Hawkins, Elizabeth C. (Box 68)
  - Hawkins, Elizabeth L. (Box 68)
  - Heinlein, Mary V. (Box 68)
  - Helyer, Mary E. (Box 68)
  - Henry, Janet M. (Box 68)
  - Hill, Louise (Box 68)
  - Hines, Helen M. (Box 68)
  - Hitchcock, Anne Wilson (Box 68)
  - Hoffheimer, Jean S. (Box 68)
  - Holihan, Edith S. (Box 68)
  - Hooker, Adelaide F. (Box 68)
  - Home, Edith L. (Box 68)
  - Horney, Anna L. (Box 68)
  - Hottenstein, Louise R. (Box 68)
  - Houck, J. Winifred (Box 68)
  - Howe, Elizabeth (Box 68)
  - Howe, Elizabeth M. (Box 68)
  - Howell, Constance (Box 68)
  - Hubbard, Anne (Box 68)
  - Hubbard, Genevieve, [EMPTY] (Box 68)
  - Hull, Elizabeth P. (Box 68)
  - Hunt, Dorothy G. (Box 68)
  - Hymes, Zilla (Box 68)
  - Ingersoll, Katherine C. (Box 68)
  - Isham, Helen (Box 68)
  - Jackson, Harriet (Box 68)
  - Jacobus, Laura C. (Box 68)
  - Jenss, Rachel M. (Box 68)
  - Jessup, Faith J. (Box 68)
  - Jessup, Mary F. (Box 68)
  - Jobe, Miriam S. (Box 68)
  - Johnson, Evelyn (Box 68)
  - Johnson, Mary L. (Box 68)
  - Joseph, Dorothy (Box 68)
  - Keany, Frances (Box 69)
  - Kellogg, V. Louise (Box 69)
  - Kellogg, Margaret (Box 69)
  - Kent, Emily A. (Box 69)
  - Kerr, K. Jarvis (Box 69)
  - Keyes, Katharine (Box 69)
  - Kimball, Mary H. (Box 69)
  - King, Katherine (Box 69)
  - Kohn, Margaret H. (Box 69)
  - Kunhardt, Hildegard (Box 69)
  - Lang, Marjorie (Box 69)
  - Lathrop, Elizabeth S. (Box 69)
  - Laurie, K. Elizabeth (Box 69)
  - Leishman, Marjorie E. (Box 69)
  - Lewis, Grace R. (Box 69)
  - Lihme, Anita H. (Box 69)
  - Locke, Agnes D. (Box 69)
  - Loeb, Madeleine H. (Box 69)
  - Long, Frances K. (Box 69)
  - Love, Dorothy W. (Box 69)
  - Lund, Rosalie (Box 69)
  - Lyon, Katharine M. (Box 69)
  - Lytle, S. Katharine (Box 69)
  - Maibrunn, Rosalie B. (Box 69)
  - Mallett, Elizabeth G. (Box 69)
  - Manley, Helene F. (Box 69)
  - Marks, Edith E. (Box 69)
  - Martin, Elizabeth W. (Box 69)
  - Marvin, Judith H. (Box 69)
  - Matthews, Margaret (Box 69)
  - Matteson, Elizabeth M. (Box 69)
  - McCall, Mary C. (Box 69)
  - McClave, Elizabeth C. (Box 69)
  - McClintock, Barbara E. (Box 69)
  - McCullough, Dorothy E. (Box 69)
  - McGrath, Dorothy A. (Box 69)
  - McKeen, Elizabeth S. (Box 69)
  - McLain, Mary B. (Box 69)
  - McPherson, Catherine E. (Box 69)
  - McPherson, M. Frances (Box 69)
  - Meneely, Eleanor M. (Box 69)
  - Merriman, Margaret M. (Box 69)
  - Metcalf, Kathleen G. (Box 69)
  - Meyer, Juliet F. (Box 69)
  - Michelson, Beatrice (Box 69)
  - Millard, Ruth A. (Box 69)
  - Miller, Pauline M. (Box 69)
  - Miller, Marion F. (Box 69)
  - Mitchell, Helen M. (Box 69)
  - Moore, Carol (Box 69)
  - Moore, Elizabeth W. (Box 69)
  - Moorhouse, Phyllis J. (Box 69)
  - Morgan, Katharine (Box 69)
  - Morley, Helen K. (Box 69)
  - Morrey, Margaret (Box 69)
  - Mott, Aimee (Box 69)
  - Moulton, E. Louise (Box 69)
  - Moulton, Ruth (Box 69)
  - Muchnic, Helen L. (Box 69)
  - Nagel, Anne D. (Box 69)
  - Neilley, Margaret P. (Box 69)
  - Nettleton, Mary T. (Box 69)
  - Newhall, Margaret E. (Box 69)
  - Nicoll, Caroline L. (Box 69)
  - Nollet, Francoise (Box 69)
  - Ohnesorge, Hedwig (Box 69)
  - Ottis, Elizabeth (Box 69)
  - Parmly, Ruth (Box 69)
  - Parrish, Lillian (Box 69)
  - Parsons, May Hall (Box 69)
  - Parvin, Doris H. (Box 69)
  - Patton, Honora J. (Box 69)
  - Pearson, Elizabeth (Box 69)
  - Peck, Mary-Ellen (Box 69)
  - Peck, Nancy (Box 69)
  - Pelton, Catherine (Box 69)
  - Perkins, Susan L. (Box 69)
  - Peterson, Virgilia (Box 69)
  - Phelan, Katharine (Box 69)
  - Philbrick, Norma (Box 69)
  - Piseck, Frederica P. (Box 69)
  - Plummer, Susan M. (Box 69)
  - Pollak, Inez (Box 69)
  - Pomeroy, Harriet B. (Box 69)
  - Porter, Louise Hoyt (Box 69)
  - Potter, Lydia A. (Box 69)
  - Potter, Mary J. (Box 69)
  - Powell, Eleanor A. (Box 69)
  - Raby, Lady Jane M. (Box 69)
  - Ransom, Eleanor (Box 69)
  - Rathbone, Eleanor (Box 69)
  - Raycroft, Myla (Box 69)
  - Reeves, Mary C. (Box 69)
  - Reiland, Virginia F. (Box 69)
  - Reyburn, Neeley (Box 69)
  - Richards, Mildred (Box 69)
  - Roemler, Marjorie (Box 69)
  - Rogers, Barbara (Box 69)
  - Rogers, Helen (Box 69)
  - Rolls, Kathaleen (Box 69)
  - Rombauer, Marion (Box 69)
  - Rosenthal, Jane (Box 69)
  - Ross, James Bruce (Box 69)
  - Ross, Katharine (Box 69)
  - Rosselet, Jeanne (Box 69)
  - Rothschild, Jane (Box 69)
  - Rowe, Helen D. (Box 69)
  - Rowley, Jean B. (Box 69)
  - Rule, Lois R. (Box 69)
  - Russell, Josephine (Box 69)
  - Rust, Nancy (Box 69)
  - Sauber, Emily J. (Box 69)
  - Saurel, Miriam (Box 69)
  - Schatz, Helen A. (Box 69)
  - Scripture, Dorothy (Box 69)
  - Scudder, Sarah R. (Box 69)
  - Selfridge, Evelyn G. (Box 69)
  - Sharp, Estelle L. (Box 69)
  - Shear, Marion E. (Box 69)
  - Sheets, Margaret H. (Box 69)
  - Shepard, Margaret D. (Box 69)
  - Shepherd, A. Virginia (Box 69)
  - Sherman, Ruth T. (Box 69)
  - Sippy, Maud L. (Box 69)
  - Skinner, Lauralee (Box 69)
  - Slattery, Mabel K. (Box 69)
  - Slingluff, Kathleen K. (Box 69)
  - Slomczanka, Marja C. (Box 69)
  - Smith, Elinor S. (Box 69)
  - Smith, Julia B. (Box 69)
  - Smith, L. Jacintha (Box 69)
  - Smith, Margaret (Box 69)
  - Smoot, Bethia P. (Box 69)
  - Southard, Elizabeth (Box 69)
  - Stadnichenko, Anna M., [EMPTY] (Box 69)
  - Staley, Eleanor O. (Box 69)
  - Steichen, Mary (Box 69)
  - Stein, Marion E. (Box 69)
  - Stern, Margaret M. (Box 69)
  - Stetson, Helen (Box 69)
  - Stocke, Lucille M. (Box 69)
  - Stocker, Sarah L. (Box 69)
  - Stockwell, Katharine R. (Box 69)
  - Story, Helen F. (Box 69)
  - Stow, A. Pauline C. (Box 69)
  - Strauss, Babette J. (Box 69)
  - Taft, Elizabeth L. (Box 70)
  - Tappan, Eleanor H. (Box 70)
  - Tardy, Dorothy F. (Box 70)
  - Taylor, Dorothy A. (Box 70)
  - Taylor, Frances (Box 70)
  - Taylor, Grace I. (Box 70)
  - Taylor, Harriet W. (Box 70)
  - Tenney, Elizabeth (Box 70)
  - Thayer, Mary Borland (Box 70)
  - Thomas, Elizabeth B. (Box 70)
  - Thomas, Elizabeth H. (Box 70)
  - Titsworth, Marian H. (Box 70)
  - Trafford, Rachel (Box 70)
  - Tucker, Helen F. (Box 70)
  - Tuthill, Elizabeth, [EMPTY] (Box 70)
  - Tyroler, Hortense E. (Box 70)
  - Uhrig, Frances S. (Box 70)
  - Upson, Eleanor M. (Box 70)
  - Urquhart, Louise W. (Box 70)
  - Valentine, Margot (Box 70)
  - Van der Veer, Grace (Box 70)
  - Van Houten, Eva M. (Box 70)
  - Van Pelt, Margaret V. (Box 70)
  - Vance, Frances S., [EMPTY] (Box 70)
  - Narcissa Vanderlip (Box 70)
  - Wagner, Mary S. (Box 70)
  - Wakelin, Helen (Box 70)
  - Walker, Eleanor P. (Box 70)
  - Walker, Harriet E. (Box 70)
  - Walter, Alice L. (Box 70)
  - Ward, Frances (Box 70)
  - Watson, Elinor B. (Box 70)
  - Weil, Helen C. (Box 70)
  - Weld, Helen (Box 70)
  - West, Alice H. (Box 70)
  - West, Anna B. (Box 70)
  - Westbrook, E. Wilhelmina (Box 70)
  - Wheeler, Lucy M. (Box 70)
  - White, Bertha D. (Box 70)
  - White, Florence D. (Box 70)
  - Whitmarsh, Martha S. (Box 70)
  - Whitney, Elinor (Box 70)
  - Wiley, Laura C. (Box 70)
  - Williams, Cordelia R. (Box 70)
  - Williams, Genevieve (Box 70)
  - Williamson, Isabel G. (Box 70)
  - Wilson, Theodora E. (Box 70)
  - Wing, Eleanor E. (Box 70)
  - Wing, Katherine C. (Box 70)
  - Winter, Gladys (Box 70)
  - Wolf, Delia E. (Box 70)
  - Wolf, Louise S. (Box 70)
  - Wolfe, Eleanor M. (Box 70)
  - Woodcock, Elizabeth F. (Box 70)
  - Woolf, Katharine (Box 70)
  - Yancey, Phebe L. (Box 70)
  - Zimmerer, Emily (Box 70)
- Class of 1926
  - Acheson, Elizabeth (Box 70)
  - Adams, Elizabeth (Box 70)
  - Alderton, Elizabeth C. (Box 70)
  - Allen, Caroline K. (Box 70)
  - Allen, Frances Y. (Box 70)
  - Antinori, Carolina M. (Box 70)
  - Archibald, Ruth F. (Box 70)
  - Maritje Babcock (Box 70)
  - Bacon, Prall G. (Box 70)
  - Frances, Anna Bailey, [EMPTY] (Box 70)
  - Baird, Ruth R. (Box 70)
  - Baldwin, Elizabeth (Box 70)
  - Baldwin, Mary G. (Box 70)
  - Baldwin, Sarah (Box 70)
  - Barnes, Mildred J. (Box 70)
  - Barney, Virginia (Box 70)
  - Bartlett, Helen W. (Box 70)
  - Bauer, Catherine K. (Box 70)
  - Beck, Elizabeth H. (Box 70)
  - Beebe, Agnes R. (Box 70)
  - Beeson, Eleanor (Box 70)
  - Belknap, Emilia F. (Box 70)
  - Berdan, Pamela R. (Box 70)
  - Bethel, Emily P. (Box 70)
  - Bicknell, Eleanor F. (Box 70)
  - Bradley, Edith R. (Box 70)
  - Bigelow, Eileen (Box 70)
  - Bigelow, Frances (Box 70)
  - Bixby, Deborah (Box 70)
  - Blackmon, Lucy C. (Box 70)
  - Boettiger, Elizabeth F. (Box 70)
  - Bolton, Laetitia T. (Box 70)
  - Borland, Harriet (Box 70)
  - Borzilleri, Eleanor (Box 70)
  - Bowie, Alice Evelyn, [EMPTY] (Box 70)
  - Boynton, Mary B. (Box 70)
  - Brace, Alice B. (Box 70)
  - Brandt, Helen (Box 70)
  - Brewster, Elizabeth B. (Box 70)
  - Brewster, Margaret V. (Box 70)
  - Bubier, Madeleine M. (Box 70)
  - Burkel, Katharine O. (Box 70)
  - Butler, Elizabeth (Box 70)
  - Button, Margaret S. (Box 70)
  - Butts, Carolyn P. (Box 70)
  - Carruth, Virginia J. (Box 70)
  - Caven, Elizabeth A. (Box 70)
  - Chace, Elinor L. (Box 70)
  - Chandler, Mary H. (Box 70)
  - Chapman, Mary (Box 70)
  - Clark, Kathryn P. (Box 70)
  - Claybrook, Judith N. (Box 70)
  - Cleveland, Susan B. (Box 70)
  - Clothier, Florence (Box 70)
  - Coggeshall, Mary (Box 70)
  - Cole, Helen C. (Box 70)
  - Comley, Marion S. (Box 70)
  - Conger, Elizabeth M., [EMPTY] (Box 70)
  - Connard, Mary H. (Box 70)
  - Conover, Mary E. (Box 70)
  - Cook, Madeline Ruth, [EMPTY] (Box 70)
  - Cooley, Rebecca M. (Box 70)
  - Cooper, Mary L. (Box 70)
  - Cornell, Arven (Box 70)
  - Craig, Mary W. (Box 70)
  - Crampton, Edith (Box 70)
  - Crawford, Pauline V. (Box 70)
  - Crocker, Charity, [EMPTY] (Box 70)
  - Crutchfield, Harriet (Box 70)
  - Curry, Elisabeth W. (Box 70)
  - Curtiss, Harriet E. (Box 70)
  - Cushman, Georgiana L. (Box 70)
  - Cushman, Josephine P. (Box 70)
  - Damon, Priscilla (Box 70)
  - Dann, Constance R. (Box 70)
  - Davis, Amy D. (Box 70)
  - Davis, Leah A., [EMPTY] (Box 70)
  - Dawson, Katharine (Box 70)
  - Day, E. Margaret (Box 70)
  - Dayton, Avis Louise (Box 70)
  - Delaporte, Renee (Box 71)
  - Dennison, Elizabeh T. (Box 71)
  - Depue, Mabel R. (Box 71)
  - Dewey, Elizabeth B. (Box 71)
  - Dismukes, Judith L. (Box 71)
  - Donaldson, Harriet (Box 71)
  - Dore, Germaine (Box 71)
  - Dortch, Louise E. (Box 71)
  - Dougan, Elisabeth R. (Box 71)
  - Driver, Ruth (Box 71)
  - Dunlop, Katharine (Box 71)
  - Dunn, Esther H., [EMPTY] (Box 71)
  - Durand, Margaret (Box 71)
  - Duvoxa, Hana (Box 71)
  - Ebert, Elisabeth R. (Box 71)
  - Edminson, Dorothy G. (Box 71)
  - Edwards, Alberta (Box 71)
  - Ellis, Presley W. (Box 71)
  - Empie, Hester (Box 71)
  - Estabrook, Helen (Box 71)
  - Evans, Elinore R. (Box 71)
  - Evans, Florence (Box 71)
  - Evans, Mildred J. (Box 71)
  - Ewing, Margaret (Box 71)
  - Eynon, M. Kathryn (Box 71)
  - Feldman, Margaret (Box 71)
  - Feldman, Pauline R. (Box 71)
  - Feldsine, Mary D. (Box 71)
  - Fenner, Elizabeth H. (Box 71)
  - Ficklin, Mary Lousie (Box 71)
  - Fite, Katherine B. (Box 71)
  - Flint, Beatrice (Box 71)
  - Folsom, Margaret (Box 71)
  - Fotheringham, Jean T. (Box 71)
  - Freeland, Louise M. (Box 71)
  - French, Catherine R. (Box 71)
  - Fuehr, Alexandra M. (Box 71)
  - Fukui, Eiko (Box 71)
  - Fuller, Louise S. (Box 71)
  - Gaillard, Anne P. (Box 71)
  - Gambrill, Merrydelle (Box 71)
  - Gannett, Mary (Box 71)
  - Gapen, Mary, [EMPTY] (Box 71)
  - Garnsey, Gertrude G. (Box 71)
  - Gatchel, Frances C. (Box 71)
  - Gatzert, Clara E. (Box 71)
  - Goetzmann, Frances B. (Box 71)
  - Goff, Frances Mary (Box 71)
  - Goldmark, Elinor (Box 71)
  - Goodale, Elaine W. (Box 71)
  - Goodman, Grace (Box 71)
  - Greene, Marian E. (Box 71)
  - Griffin, Mary A. (Box 71)
  - Gwynne, Edith M. (Box 71)
  - Hageman, Charlotte S. (Box 71)
  - Hall, Alice K. (Box 71)
  - Hall, Rosalie G. (Box 71)
  - Hall, Lucy (Box 71)
  - Hamilton, Katherine (Box 71)
  - Hamlin, Elizabeth W. (Box 71)
  - Hammond, Josephine S. (Box 71)
  - Harden, Margaret P. (Box 71)
  - Harris, E. Melinda, [EMPTY] (Box 71)
  - Harris, Elizabeth (Box 71)
  - Harris, Muriel G. (Box 71)
  - Hasbrouck, Ruth I. (Box 71)
  - Haskell, Juliet (Box 71)
  - Hawes, Adelaide D. (Box 71)
  - Hawley, Kathleen H. (Box 71)
  - Hayes, Alice (Box 71)
  - Haywood, Eloise T. (Box 71)
  - Head, Elizabeth L. (Box 71)
  - Hensel, L. Ruth (Box 71)
  - Hickok, Louise A. (Box 71)
  - Hill, Catherine W. (Box 71)
  - Hill, Katherine (Box 71)
  - Hoffman, Hester (Box 71)
  - Hoogland, Helen T. (Box 71)
  - Hopkins, Marion (Box 71)
  - Howbert, Elizabeth M. (Box 71)
  - Howland, Esther (Box 71)
  - Hufnagel, Dorothy K. (Box 71)
  - Hyde, Beatrice I. (Box 71)
  - Hyde, Elizabeth (Box 71)
  - Ibanez, Carmen (Box 71)
  - Irwin, C. Katherine (Box 71)
  - Jessup, Mary E. (Box 71)
  - Jewell, Elizabeth J. (Box 71)
  - Johnson, Erma M. (Box 71)
  - Johnson, Jeannette E. (Box 71)
  - Johnson, Katharine D., [EMPTY] (Box 71)
  - Johnson, Martha (Box 71)
  - Jones, Katharine (Box 71)
  - Kelby, Adelaide (Box 71)
  - Kellogg, Mary P. (Box 71)
  - Kelsey, Mary Alice (Box 71)
  - Kennedy, Leontine M. (Box 71)
  - Keogh, Cornelia R. (Box 71)
  - Kepler, Helen, [EMPTY] (Box 71)
  - Kernan, Mary S. (Box 71)
  - Kingman, Eleanor (Box 71)
  - Kinmont, E. Louise (Box 71)
  - Knight, Eleanor A. (Box 71)
  - Knowlton, Catharine M. (Box 71)
  - Knox, H. Rebecca (Box 71)
  - Korey, Ruth A. (Box 71)
  - Kuhn, Emma S. (Box 71)
  - LaBoiteaux, Lydia Mitchell (Box 71)
  - Lacey, Ruth E. (Box 71)
  - Lamport, Helen (Box 71)
  - Lansingh, Emily S. (Box 71)
  - Lasker, Mary (Box 71)
  - Leach, Susan M. (Box 71)
  - Leale, Bianca M. (Box 71)
  - Lechtman, Esther C. (Box 71)
  - Lee, Nancy (Box 71)
  - Lewis, Martha C. (Box 71)
  - Liebman, Eleanor (Box 71)
  - Lipscomb, Rebekah B. (Box 71)
  - Loomis, Florence I. (Box 71)
  - Louchheim, Margaret (Box 71)
  - Love, Harriet (Box 71)
  - Lucas, Esther (Box 71)
  - Lundborg, Alfhild M. (Box 71)
  - Lunn, Mabel C. (Box 71)
  - Lyon, Mary-Phillips (Box 71)
  - Manley, Dorothy E. (Box 71)
  - Marr, Helen W. (Box 71)
  - Marshall, Mary K. (Box 71)
  - McBroom, Nellis V. (Box 71)
  - McCammon, Althea M. (Box 71)
  - McClellan, Ruth (Box 71)
  - McLachlan, Marjorie R. (Box 71)
  - Melone, Elizabeth B. (Box 71)
  - Melone, Theodora G. (Box 71)
  - Metcalf, Marjorie L. (Box 71)
  - Meyers, Margaret F. (Box 71)
  - Miller, Katharine S. (Box 71)
  - Milmine, Charlotte P. (Box 71)
  - Moore, Mildred E. (Box 71)
  - Morgan, Helen L. (Box 71)
  - Morley, Julia H. (Box 71)
  - Morrill, Elizabeth (Box 71)
  - Morse, Martha J. (Box 71)
  - Mosher, Helen E. (Box 71)
  - Moss, Anna H. (Box 71)
  - Murray, Janet H. (Box 71)
  - Nardi, D. Zita (Box 71)
  - Nason, Margaret (Box 71)
  - Nason, Mary M. (Box 71)
  - Newstedt, Elizabeth T. (Box 72)
  - Noble-Jones, Frances M. (Box 72)
  - Norris, Elinor R. (Box 72)
  - Oakford, Frances S. (Box 72)
  - Olson, Helen A. (Box 72)
  - Osborn, Mary E. (Box 72)
  - Palmer, Elizabeth C. (Box 72)
  - Patten, E. Eugenia (Box 72)
  - Paxton, Carolyn (Box 72)
  - Peck, Mary Gray (Box 72)
  - Perego, Ruth S. (Box 72)
  - Pigott, Anna Lou (Box 72)
  - Pollak, Katherine H. (Box 72)
  - Poole, Hulda (Box 72)
  - Post, Dorothy I. (Box 72)
  - Price, Alberta D. (Box 72)
  - Pritchard, H. Winifred (Box 72)
  - Quimby, Anne F. (Box 72)
  - Reeve, Hazel E. (Box 72)
  - Reid, Dorothy (Box 72)
  - Reilly, Frances C. (Box 72)
  - Reimer, Isabelle E. (Box 72)
  - Rhodes, Elizabeth, [EMPTY] (Box 72)
  - Ribbel, Marjorie (Box 72)
  - Robinson, Virginia A. (Box 72)
  - Robinson, Ruth E. (Box 72)
  - Rollinson, Keturah C. (Box 72)
  - Rosanoff, Elizabeth P. (Box 72)
  - Rosenthal, Jeanne (Box 72)
  - Roylance, Elizabeth (Box 72)
  - Rudisill, Harriet R. (Box 72)
  - Rulofson, Carol C. (Box 72)
  - Ruperti, Sallie M. (Box 72)
  - Russel, Katharine S. (Box 72)
  - Russell, Margaret (Box 72)
  - Sailer, Agnes (Box 72)
  - Sanborn, Elizabeth (Box 72)
  - Schamberg, Lucille (Box 72)
  - Schermerhorn, Margaret B. (Box 72)
  - Schmidt, Katharine (Box 72)
  - Schueller, Margaret E. (Box 72)
  - Schukraft, Jane J. (Box 72)
  - Scott, Madelaine N. (Box 72)
  - Sheldon, Janet B. (Box 72)
  - Sherman, Elizabeth H. (Box 72)
  - Shurlock, Elisabeth W. (Box 72)
  - Singer, Elizabeth (Box 72)
  - Slocum, D. Anne (Box 72)
  - Small, Elizabeth (Box 72)
  - Small, Molly (Box 72)
  - Smith, Constance C. (Box 72)
  - Smith, Helen D. (Box 72)
  - Smith, Theodora E. (Box 72)
  - Southwick, Mildred D. (Box 72)
  - Spafford, Madeline (Box 72)
  - Spross, Gertrude L. (Box 72)
  - Srbkova, Ludmila K. (Box 72)
  - Steedman, Katherine (Box 72)
  - Steffens, Marion F. (Box 72)
  - Stein, Kathryn W. (Box 72)
  - Stevenson, Frances A. (Box 72)
  - Stivers, Mary V. (Box 72)
  - Stocking, Harriet P. (Box 72)
  - Stokes, Martha K. (Box 72)
  - Swift, Mary Laing (Box 72)
  - Taber, L. Starr (Box 72)
  - Tanner, Louise W. (Box 72)
  - Taylor, Anne R. (Box 72)
  - Taylor, Helen King (Box 72)
  - Thomas, Aimee J. (Box 72)
  - Toogood, Catherine L. (Box 72)
  - Turner, Lucia F. (Box 72)
  - Tyler, Charlotte A. (Box 72)
  - Van De Water, Dorothy (Box 72)
  - Van Duyn, Mary L. (Box 72)
  - van Ingen, Wilhelmina (Box 72)
  - Van Loon, Louise S. (Box 72)
  - Varney, Frances E. (Box 72)
  - Vihervaara, Annalusa (Box 72)
  - Wadleigh, Elizabeth G. (Box 72)
  - Walbridge, Elizabeth S. (Box 72)
  - Walker, Margaret M. (Box 72)
  - Walker, Marjory E. (Box 72)
  - Walter, Henrietta E. (Box 72)
  - Warbasse, Helen D. (Box 72)
  - Waring, Alice (Box 72)
  - Way, Helen E. (Box 72)
  - Weed, Emily L. (Box 72)
  - Westcott, Mary D. (Box 72)
  - Whitlock, Margaret Y. (Box 72)
  - Wildey, Virginia M. (Box 72)
  - Wilson, Muriel R. (Box 72)
  - Wilson, Theodora W. (Box 72)
  - Wood, Charlotte (Box 72)
  - Yeomans, Annis S. (Box 72)
- Class of 1927
  - Adams, Marion (Box 72)
  - Addoms, Margaret K. (Box 72)
  - Allen, Grace W. (Box 72)
  - Anderson, Elizabeth M. (Box 72)
  - Antonescu, Daniela Maria Z. (Box 72)
  - Arbuckle, Virginia K. (Box 72)
  - Armstrong, Eugenia K. (Box 72)
  - Atwater, Helen (Box 72)
  - Auchincloss, E. Ellen (Box 72)
  - Bailey, Barbara (Box 72)
  - Baker, Carolyn (Box 72)
  - Baker, Marion J. (Box 72)
  - Bancroft, Barbara (Box 72)
  - Banes, Margaret (Box 72)
  - Bangs, Ruth (Box 72)
  - Barclay, Josephine (Box 72)
  - Barker, Anne (Box 72)
  - Barnes, Evelyn E. (Box 72)
  - Barnes, Martha V. (Box 72)
  - Baxter, Katherine F. (Box 72)
  - Belcher, Barbara (Box 72)
  - Bernheim, Minda B. (Box 72)
  - Betts, Mary H. (Box 72)
  - Blake, Barbara (Box 72)
  - Blake, Charlotte D. (Box 72)
  - Blaney, Elizabeth H. (Box 72)
  - Block, Miriam (Box 72)
  - Bogart, Mary E. (Box 72)
  - Bonbright, Eleanor D. (Box 72)
  - Boocock, Mary (Box 72)
  - Booraem, Cornelia V. (Box 72)
  - Borg, Margit R. (Box 72)
  - Bouck, Polly (Box 72)
  - Bourne, Emma C. (Box 72)
  - Bowen, Mary H. (Box 72)
  - Brackett, Mary (Box 72)
  - Braislin, Alice C. (Box 72)
  - Braitmayer, Josephine (Box 72)
  - Brantingham, Kathryn E. (Box 72)
  - Breck, Katharine P. (Box 72)
  - Breckinridge, M. Marvin (Box 72)
  - Brewster, Virginia S. (Box 72)
  - Brooking, Julia (Box 72)
  - Brown, Alburta H. (Box 72)
  - Brunnow, Marguerite (Box 72)
  - Bullitt, Priscilla C. (Box 73)
  - Burrell, Virginia (Box 73)
  - Butcher, Marion S. (Box 73)
  - Buttenwieser, Gertrude C. (Box 73)
  - Butterfield, Laura M. (Box 73)
  - Cady, Marion, [EMPTY] (Box 73)
  - Carr, Elizabeth (Box 73)
  - Carruth, Lucy R. (Box 73)
  - Cary, Winifred K. (Box 73)
  - Chapman, Lucia M. (Box 73)
  - Chase, Cecilia J. (Box 73)
  - Chickering, Mary C. (Box 73)
  - Clarke, Gertrude (Box 73)
  - Clausen, Hilda (Box 73)
  - Cluverius, Martha (Box 73)
  - Coleman, Constance (Box 73)
  - Colgate, M. Evelyn (Box 73)
  - Collens, Margaret L. (Box 73)
  - Comstock, Janet T. (Box 73)
  - Cook, Katharine S. (Box 73)
  - Cooley, Emily H. (Box 73)
  - Corcoran, Celeste (Box 73)
  - Cornelison, Margaret L. (Box 73)
  - Covington, Anne (Box 73)
  - Cox, Emma Lee (Box 73)